lawpay.com 2019-04-17

# LawPay | Terms and Conditions

## Privacy Policy

As part of AffiniPay’s long tradition of trust, the confidentiality of personal and business information is paramount. We maintain high standards in order to safeguard personal information. We will remain vigilant in protecting that information and in using it in a fair and lawful manner. 

#### To what does this Online Privacy Statement apply?

This Online Privacy Statement applies to the personal and business information that we collect from or about you via this  www.LawPay.com  web site (this “Site”). This Site may contain links to other web sites, and this Online Privacy Statement does not apply to those sites. If you link to any of those sites, we recommend that you review their privacy policies. If we change our privacy policies or practices, we will also change this Online Privacy Statement. 

####  What personal and technical information do we collect via this Site? 

This Site will collect personal and business information that you voluntarily provide, such as your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address. This Site may also collect information on your preferences, such as language selection; information on which pages within this Site you visit; and certain technical information regarding your computer and operating systems, such as your Internet protocol address, domain name and system configurations and settings. We will not know who you are unless you tell us. 

####  How do we use, share and secure personal information that we collect via this Site? 

The information you give us is absolutely safe with us. We will never rent, sell, share or otherwise disclose your personal information to third parties. We may, however, contact you periodically regarding your account or any service you have subscribed to. We may also send you promotional announcements from time to time about new products and services that you might find useful. You may opt out from receiving information from us at any time. 

#### How do we use cookies?

On this Site, we may use cookies or other technology to gather information about Site usage to help us improve the content, usability and functionality of this Site, and to remember your personal settings, such as language selection. This will help us understand how many new and repeat users visit this Site, which features or pages are most popular, and user browsing and usage patterns. 

####  What if you have your browser set with privacy preferences? 

This Site may contain information, including Privacy Preference Information (“P3P”), intended to work with your selected privacy preferences. While we have tried to make such Privacy Preference Information included within this Site conform to this full-text Online Privacy Statement, this Online Privacy Statement is the definitive statement of privacy policies and practices for this Site. 

#### Live Chat

We use live chat to assist you with questions about our products. If our live chat is offline we will collect your name and email address so that we may reply to your request.
